{
    "subject": "resource/Too_Phat",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Too Phat",
    "human_readable": "The name of Too Phat is Too Phat.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.968488872051239,
            "question": "What is the name of Too Phat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506331086158752,
            "question": "Is Too Phat a person's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8567453622817993,
            "question": "Does the name 'Too Phat' have any special meaning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8526878356933594,
            "question": "What kind of context might involve the name 'Too Phat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8346524238586426,
            "question": "Is there anything else associated with the name 'Too Phat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8335063457489014,
            "question": "Could 'Too Phat' be a band or group's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8210840821266174,
            "question": "What comes to mind when you hear the name 'Too Phat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804564237594604,
            "question": "How would you use the name 'Too Phat' in a sentence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7327608466148376,
            "question": "Could 'Too Phat' refer to something else besides a person or group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5693329572677612,
            "question": "What other information could we learn about Too Phat?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Too Phat is Too Phat.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4485_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'Too Phat' refer to something else besides a person or group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4485_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you use the name 'Too Phat' in a sentence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4485_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What comes to mind when you hear the name 'Too Phat'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4485_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4485_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Yes.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**\n\nToo Phat's name remains unchanged, and that's a fact."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Yes, the name of Too Phat is indeed Too Phat."
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The name \"Too Phat\" suggests a focus on lyrical content, but the provided context information shows that Too Phat is more focused on local influences and hip-hop tracks based on Asli loops, Sharifah Aini samples, and even local humour. This indicates that the group's name might be misleading in terms of their actual style and sound.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}